A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller, Sr. papers FA002
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence, 1804-1896; C; 34.4 Cubic Feet 86 boxes
  - Business Investments, I; 6 Cubic Feet 15 boxes
    - Gleason - Gruebnther, 79 Pages (Reel 4, Frame 0706, Box 77, Folder 572)
      Gleason, C. W., 2/16/1893. New York, New York. Request for loan; broker of iron mines. Gleichner, L., 10/18/1891. Pomona, California. Offer of gold and silver mining lands in Arizona. Goble, L. S., 9/16/1890. New York, New York. Insurance premium for W. E. Clarke. Goldman, Leon, 3/21/1892. New York, New York. Seeks interview. Gorham, J. M., 5/5-8/1890. Cleveland, Ohio. Washboard trust plan. Gostling, C. P., 2/3/1893. Bellaire, Ohio. Cement industry investment offer. Gould, George J., 1892. New York, New York. Wabash St. Louis & Pacific Railroad Company proxy; conflict with O. D. Ashley. Gould, Jay, 1889. Unidentified location. Article on plans for Missouri, Kansas & Texas Railway Company and richmond West Point Terminal Railway & Warehouse Company; H. K. Enos. Gracie, A., 4/1892. New York, New York. Investment in irrigation project in Texas. Grady, C. P., 9/1886-9/1890. Baltimore, Maryland, and Duluth, Minnesota. Real estate broker; offers coal and timberlands in West Virginia and iron ore lands in Minnesota and Canada. Graham, E. S., 5/16/1891. Graham, Texas. Railroad investment offer; extension of Missouri, Kansas, & Texas Railway Company. Granger, S. O., 12/22/1891. Cartersville, Georgia. Iron mine offer in Georgia; Etowah Iron Company. Grant Brothers, 1/31/1891. New York, New York. Investment offer. Gray, C. L., 1/28/1892. New York, New York. New York Bank Note Company; wants to bid on New York Transit Company bond engraving and printing. Gray, J. D., 5/14/1890. Astoria, Oregon. Real estate offer for shipbuilding plant. Greenwood, A. G., 7/24/1893. Chicago, Illinois. Offers gold mine investment in South Dakota. Gregory, G. F., 2/10/1888. New York, New York. Standard Oil Company, domestic trade department; railroad scheme of Dalrymple brothers. Grey, W., 9/1890. London, England. Railroad investment offer in England; Midland Tramways Company. Griffin, A., 3/6/1893. Washington, D. C. Automatic car coupler invention. Grover, W. G., 12/24/1886. Hamer, North Carolina. Mineral investment offer in North Carolina. Grovesteen, W., 8/25/1891. New York, New York. Investment offer. Griscom, C. A., 1889-1892. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Borrowed $220,000 for purchase of Standard Oil Trust shares; International Navigation Company; Northern Pacific Railroad Company construction of whaleback steamers. Griswold, C., 6/19/1885. New York, New York. Steel mill investment offer; Albany & Rensselaer Iron & Steel Company. Gruaz, T., 1889-1890. East St. Louis, Illinois. Coal, salt, and farm lands investment offers in Illinois, Kansas, and Missouri. Guenther, E. G., 10/7/1881. Cleveland, Ohio. Bookbinding receipt.
    - Hagan - Hatch, 137 Pages (Box 77, Folder 573, Reel 4, Frame 0785)
      Hagan, C. L., 1892. Charleston, West Virginia. coal lands in West Virginia. Haine, L. J., undated. Unidentified location. Request for loan on Standard Oil Company stock. Hall, A. S., 11/25/1889. Baltimore, New York. Offers orange grove investment in Florida. Hall, J., 8/289/1893. New York, New York. Manufacturing investment offer. Hall, W. B., 10/26/1886. Cleveland, Ohio. Receipt for sale of shares of Britton Iron & Steel Company to H. C. Rouse. Halls, W., 7/2-9/1886. New York, New York. Receipts for payment on call loans; Hanover National Bank. Hamilton, A., 1/21/1890. Etna, Georgia. Offers ore lands in Georgia. Hamilton, E. P., 2/14/1890. New York, New York. Offers real estate near Cleveland, Ohio. Hamilton, J. L., 6/9/1890. Hopeston, Illinois. Bond offer for Georgia railroad. Hammond, C. A., 7/25/1891. Boston, Massachusetts. Investment in offer in Boston, Revere Beach & Lynn Railroad; competition with Boston & Maine Railroad. Hammond, W. I., 3/11/1891. New York, New York. Sends information on W. O. Rand Company of Chicago, Illinois. Hanna, Marcus A. and H. M., 3/1887-8/1893. Cleveland, Ohio. Loans from John D. Rockefeller; purchased iron ore from John D. Rockefeller mines. Hannahs, J. M., 4/1886-5/1/1893. New York, New York. Broadway elevated railway scheme; Chicago, Illinois elevated railway scheme. Hanover National Bank, 1886-1893. New York, New York. Dividend checks; interest rates on loans. Harkness, C. W., 11/11/1893. Cleveland Ohio. Appointment with John D. Rockefeller. Harkness, D. M., 1884. Unidentified location. John D. Rockefeller loan on Standard Oil Trust shares. Harkness, S. V., 4/4/1886-2/8/1888. Cleveland, Ohio. Proposes pipeline for Cincinnati, Ohio, water supply; accepts investment share in steamship company. Harper, W. R., 3/3/1888. New Haven, Connecticut. Sends stock in Hebrew Society; Correspondence School of Hebrew. Harraman & Tuttle, 2/17-27/1891. New York, New York. Quigley, Harraman & Tuttle, bankers and brokers; offer bonds. Harris, Robert, 1882-1892. New York, New York. Northern Pacific Railroad Company president; proxies; relations with other railroads; applies for job as president, Missouri, Kansas & Texas Railway Company. Harrison, D. F., 6/14/1890-7/14/1890. Ringgold, Pennsylvania. Offers coal lands in Pennsylvania. Harrison, James, 6/29/1886-7/20/1886. Atlanta, Georgia. Marble quarry business opportunity in Georgia; brochure of Seattle, Washington, Board of Trade. Hassall, W. S., 11/1889-2/1890. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Iron lands development in Pennsylvania; brother-in-law of T. Tolman. Hatch & Foote, 1893. New York, New York. Investment offers; bankers. Hatch, J. L., 9/7/1893. Rochester, New York. Offers coal lands in West Virginia.
      Researchers must use microfilm. See Reels 4 and 5, located in the Index Room, Cabinet 2, Drawer 11.; Researchers must use microfilm; see Reel 4, Frame 0785.
    - Hay - Houghton, 144 Pages (Box 77, Folder 574, Reel 4, Frame 0922)
      Hay, W. G., 8/13/1889. Uniontown, Pennsylvania. Electric power plant offer. Hayen, G. A., 1/3/1888. New York, New York. Offers municipal bonds in Kansas for extensionof Chicago, Rock Island & Pacific Railroad. Hayes, J. O., 1892. Ironwood, Michigan. Loan renewal and collateral; Ashland Iron Mining Company. Hayes, S. C., 10/28/1890. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Offers land in New Jersey. Hayes, W. J. & Sons, 4/12/1888-10/10/1892. Cleveland, Ohio. Offers Ohio state bonds; Superior, Wisconsin, Rapid Transit Railway Company bonds. Hays, J. S., 7/1890-1/1893. Cleveland, Ohio. Offers mineral lands in Colorado; owes John D. Rockefeller money. Hedenberg, J. W., 3/15/1890. Washington, D. C. Offers syndicate participation; legislation. Hedges, E. C., 2/6/1890. Denver, Colorado. Offers investments in Denver real estate. Hedrick, H. R., 12/4/1890. Tacoma, Washington. Offers farm mortgages in Washington. Height, H. B., 2/15/1890. Troy, New York. Offers farmland and tannery. Henderson, J., 2/1887-3/1887. New York, New York. Has Bessemer process patents. Herbert, W. P., 5/18/1887. New York, New York. Has patents for producing gas from wood. Herrick, H. H., 4/7/1891. New York, New York. Offers mortgages in city. Heyward, W. N., 1/25/1890. Hardeeville, South Carolina. Has fiber plant that surpasses jute. Hilands, W. J., 1890-1893. Cleveland, Ohio. Investment offers in Virginia, Ohio and Colorado real estate and mortgages; stocks. Hill, E. A., 5/2/1891. Cincinnati, Ohio. Ground rent offer in Cleveland, Ohio; Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago & St. Louis Railway Company. Hill, J. H., 10/1889. Sioux City, Iowa. Offers coal and gas lands in Iowa and Wyoming; Sioux City & Wyoming Coal & Oil Land Company. Hillam, J. H., 1892-1893. New York, New York. Offers business investments. Hillyer, M. P., 1893. Topeka, Kansas. Offers investment in railroad in Tennessee and Alabama. Hitchcock, P. M., 4/1886-6/1888. Cleveland, Ohio. Offers coal lands in Virginia and real estate in California. H. M. Flagler acquaintance. Hitchings, H. M., 10/28/1889. New York, New York. Essick Printing Telegraph stock offer. Hobson, A. A., 3/13/1891. Bristol, Tennessee. Offers coal land in Kentucky. Holbrooks, F. W., 5/1888-6/1888. New York, New York. Offers land investment; pneumatic tube device. Hoiroun, J. L., 5/30/1890. Charleston, South Carolina. Offers cottonseed oil mill investment at Florence, South Carolina. Holden, L. S., 2/21/1890. St. Louis, Missouri. Offers land in Forest Park. Holgate, G., 11/8-14/1893. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. New process for manufacturing white lead; Association of American Inventors. Holland, J., 2/12/1889. Baltimore, Maryland. Offers gas system investment in Baltimore. Hollins & Company, 1890. New York, New York. Investment offers; railroad bonds. Hollister & Babcock, 1891. New York, New York. Investment offers; St. Paul & Northern Pacific Railway Company bonds. Hollister, U. S., 1/19/1891. New York, New York. Mortgage offers. Holt, J. W., 8/21/1889. Moshannon, Pennsylvania. Offers coal lands in Pennsylvania. Hopper, G. H., 2/20/1891. New York, New York. Railroad investment offer; Standard Oil Company employee. Horton, E. F., 8/21/1891. Cleveland, Ohio. Offers coal lands in Alabama; Gulf coke & Coal Company. Hotchkiss, C. A., 1/1891-11/1891. Bridgeport, Connecticut, and Baltimore, Maryland. Investment offer for Baltimore nut and bolt factory. Houghton, H. C., 1893. New York, New York. Payments on mortgages. Howard, C., 6/8/1893. Chicago, Illinois. Looking for a position with a railroad. Howard, D. B., 9/28/1888. Cleveland, Ohio. Standard Oil Company payments to Western Union Telegraph Company for August. Howard, D. C., 3/3/1890-10/14/1892. Cleveland, Ohio. Offers Western rock salt mine; offers real estate development bonds in Washington.
    - Hoyt, Colgate, July 1882-September 1886; 94 Pages (Reel 5, Frame 0001, Box 77, Folder 575)
      New York, New York. James B. Colgate & Company; brokers; Union Pacific Railroad Company; Northern Pacific Railroad Company; Missouri Pacific Railroad Company; Missouri, Kansas & Texas Railway Company; railroad stocks; loan margin account; political activities; iron mining properties in Michigan and Wisconsin.
    - Hoyt, Colgate, October 1886-1887; 87 Pages (Reel 5, Frame 0095, Box 77, Folder 576)
    - Hoyt, Colgate, 1888-February 1889; 83 Pages (Box 77, Folder 577, Reel 5, Frame 0182)
    - Hoyt, Colgate, April 1889-April 1890; 90 Pages (Box 78, Folder 578, Reel 5, Frame 0265)
    - Hoyt, Colgate, May 1890-1893; 77 Pages (Box 78, Folder 579, Reel 5, Frame 0355)
    - Hoyt, E. - Hymer, 81 Pages (Reel 5, Frame 0432, Box 78, Folder 580)
      Hoyt, Elton, 1888-1892. Cleveland, Ohio. Cashing coupons from Florida investment; brokers. Hoyt, George, 4/13/1888. Cleveland, Ohio. Offers investment in new Cleveland trust company. Hoyt, J. H., 1892. Cleveland, Ohio. Offers Western Reserve National Bank Company stock conditioned on business brought to bank; illness of Colgate Hoyt; consolidation of Michigan and Wisconsin iron mines. Hubby, F. W., 7/28/1891. Cleveland, Ohio. Offers investment in California; Bear Valley Irrigation Company. Huck, W. W., 6/26/1893. New Orleans, Louisiana. South American steamship line offer. Hudson, W. T., 1888. New York, New York, and Cleveland, Ohio. Standard Oil Company and John D. Rockefeller office information. Huffman, G. P., 5/12/1891. Dayton, Ohio. Sewing machine company bonds; Davis Sewing Machine Company. Hughes, J. H., 4/5/1891. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Offers timberlands in Pennsylvania. Hull, F. A., 12/6/1886. Danbury, Connecticut. Offers timberlands in Kentucky and Tennessee. Huntington, E., 10/21/1890-11/6/1893. New York, New York. Sending $1,000 on deposit with John D. Rockefeller. Hutchins, H. A., 12/1885-1/1893. Cleveland, Ohio. Investment possibilities; loans to Hutchins; Standard Oil Company treasurer. Hutchinson, G., 6/1889-6/1890. New York, New York. Smelting investment offer; steam engine patent. Hyman, T. J., 4/4/1888. Milwaukee, Wisconsin. Central Associated Lines earnings. Hymer, I. B., 4/23/1886. New York, New York. Investment opportunity.
    - I, 93 Pages (Box 78, Folder 581, Reel 5, Frame 0519)
      Idlewild Fruit Company, 1890. Citra, Florida. Articles of Incorporation and annual report. Illinois Steel Company, 1889. Chicago, Illinois. Consolidation with Union Steel Company. Importers & Traders National Bank, 3/7/1884. New York, New York. John D. Rockefeller loan cancelled note. Indiana Pipe Line Company, 3/15/1893. New York, New York. Notice of dividend declared. Inman & International Steamship Company, 1887-1890. Liverpool, England. John D. Rockefeller stock purchases. International & Mortgage Bank of Mexico, 1886. New York, New York. Prospectus for stock offering. Inslee, D. K., 4/4/1891. Fairhaven, Washington. Offers real estate investments. Irish, W. E., 10/1/1890. Brooklyn Village, Ohio. Offers investment in inventions and patents; United Electric Company. Ives, B., 3/25/1886. New York, New York. Statement of Northern Pacific Railroad Company, 1886-1886; brokers. Ives, W. I., 11/30/1892. New York, New York. Forwards prospectus for unidentified metal import business firm.
    - Jackson - Jennings Trust Company, 57 Pages (Box 78, Folder 582, Reel 5, Frame 0606)
      Jackson, J. R., 8/1890-9/1890. Chicago, Illinois. Real estate broker; offers feeder cattle investment in Montana and Texas. B. F. Jacobs & Company, 1892. Chicago, Illinois. Canal and rail facilities for sale; real estate broker. James, C. T., 10/17/1891. New York, New York. Real estate broker. James, F. W., 8/27/1885. Baird, Texas. Offers bank stock. James, J. G., 1885. Wichita Falls, Texas. Offers bank stock. Jaques, C. W., 10/7/1893. Ashtabula, Ohio. Requests information on steel plant investment. Jarvis-Conklin Mortgage Trust Company, 1888-1889. New York, New York. Broker; offers securities. Jefferys, W., 7/1888-9/1890. New York, New York. Railroad bridge company--crossing Hudson at Peekskill; Hudson Suspension Bridge & New England Railway Company. Jenkins, J. A., 10/4/1893. New York, New York. Accounting of vouchers for John D. Rockefeller investment. Jennings Trust Company, 11/4/1892. Chicago, Illinois. Check enclosed for railway bond.
    - Jesup Lamont, 1882-1885; 84 Pages (Box 78, Folder 583, Reel 5, Frame 0663)
      New York, New York. Brokers; account balances; railroad stocks; market conditions; cipher codes; margin accounts; Standard Oil Trust; Chicago, Milwaukee & St. Paul Railway Company; Richmond & West Point Terminal; Richmond & Danville Railroad; Union Pacific Railroad; Northern Pacific Railroad; Burlington, Cedar Rapids & Northern bonds; Missouri, Kansas & Texas Railway bonds.
    - Jesup Lamont, 1886-1887; 96 Pages (Reel 5, Frame 0747, Box 78, Folder 584)
    - Jesup Lamont, 1888-1889; 83 Pages (Reel 5, Frame 0843, Box 78, Folder 585)
    - Jesup Lamont, January-July 1890; 102 Pages (Reel 5, Frame 0926, Box 79, Folder 586)
    - Jesup Lamont, August-December 1890; 72 Pages (Box 79, Folder 587, Reel 6, Frame 0001)
    - Jesup Lamont, 1891; 102 Pages (Box 79, Folder 588, Reel 6, Frame 0073)
    - Jesup Lamont (Grouped by Security), 1892; 61 Pages (Box 79, Folder 589, Reel 6, Frame 0175)
    - Jesup Lamont (General)Jesup Lamont (General), 1892; 73 Pages (Box 79, Folder 590, Reel 6, Frame 0236)
    - Jesup Lamont (Grouped by Security), 1893; 109 Pages (Box 79, Folder 591, Reel 6, Frame 0309)
    - Jesup Lamont (General), 1893; 85 Pages (Box 79, Folder 592, Reel 6, Frame 0418)
    - Jocelyn - Jones Pratt, 113 Pages (Box 80, Folder 593, Reel 6, Frame 0503)
      Jocelyn, A. H., 2/3/1891. New York, New York. Railroad and land scheme of Ogden Pell. Johnsen, C. G., 1/1890-11/1891. New Orleans, Louisiana. Sugar cane processing scheme. Johnson, F. R., 12/1888-5/1889. New York, New York. Offers securities; broker. Johnson, G. B., 5/1888-1/1894. New York, New York. Loans by John D. Rockefeller on Standard Oil Trust and Natural Gas Trust collateral; Standard Oil Company employee. Joliet Steel Company, 1889-1890. Chicago, Illinois. Stockholder notices. Jones, C. W., 10/3/1887. New York, New York. Payment on Frank Rockefeller loan. Jones, E. D., 4/1883-1/1886. New York, New York. Offers securities; broker. Jones, S. M., 7/31/1889. Baird, Texas. Railroad enterprise in Texas. Jones & Pratt, 12/11/1886. Atlanta, Georgia. Cottonseed oil mill; brokers.
    - Jordan - Judson, 50 Pages (Box 80, Folder 594, Reel 6, Frame 0616)
      Jordan, W. T., 3/1890-7/1893. Denver, Colorado. Investigates real estate mortgage opportunities in Denver; Continental Oil Company employee. Joseph, I., 8/22/1890. New York, New York. Offers real estate on Wall Street. Joslyn, O. W., 1/1886-10/1890. New York, New York. Offers securities. Judson, E., 3/18/1893. New York, New York. Acknowledges statement of account; Memorial Baptist Church pastor.
    - K, 58 Pages (Reel 6, Frame 0666, Box 80, Folder 595)
      Kasson, C. V., 3/18/1889. Chicago, Illinois. Asks John D. Rockefeller to endorse Otis elevators in Cleveland. Keeler, H. R., 1890-1891. Cleveland, Ohio. Used insurance policies as collateral for John D. Rockefeller loan. Keith, B., 1888. New York, New York. Irrigation scheme in Arizona. Keith, Walter L., 6/17/1892. Cleveland, Ohio. Offers investment in product from oil refuse. Kemp, W., 2/24/1888. Troy, New York. Troy Sheet & Iron Company; sending interest payment. Francis B. Kemp & Company, 5/1/1890. Roanoke, Virginia. Real estate agents. Kent, G. H., 5/1/1885. New York, New York. Announcement of move; South Pennsylvania Railroad Syndicate. Kimball, G. H., 11/1889. Cleveland, Ohio. Pensacola & Memphis Railroad investment offer; Lake Superior & Michigan Southern Railway Company chief engineer. King, E. W., 2/8/1892. Great Falls, Montana. Great Falls Water Company investment offer. King, H. R., 4/19/1889. New York, New York. Offers real estate in city. King, John H., 10/13/1891. Washington, D. C. Offers investment in cement plant in South Dakota. King, John S., 11/22/1890. Chicago, Illinois. Offers real estate in Chicago. Kingston, P., 4/1/1891. Princeton, New Jersey. Offers investment in rapid transit system. Kinsman, F. E., 3/11/1891. New York, New York. Railroad signal system inventor and patentee. Kintner, C. J., 11/13/1893. New York, New York. Telephone exchange invention. Kissle, A., 5/13/1886. New York, New York. Richmond & West Point Terminal Railway & Warehouse Company; banker. Kline, A., 12/22/1892. New York, New York. Grain business. Kountze Brothers, 6/16/1885. New York, New York. Offer Omaha, Nebraska, and other municipal bonds; bankers. Knox, A., 10/31/1893. Seattle, Washington. Iron ore lands in Washington. W. C. Knox & Company, 9/8/1888. Topeka, Kansas. Offers real estate in Kansas. Kraetzer, J. M., 12/25/1893. West Acton, Massachusetts. Requests information on oil certificates. Kraft, W. D., 6/28/1893. New York, New York. Offers Brooklyn City Railroad stock; Standard Oil Company employee.
    - H. L. - Lathrop, Smith Oliphant, 40 Pages (Reel 6, Frame 0724, Box 80, Folder 596)
      H[enry?] L[ewis?], 11/29/1886. Unidentified location. Reports on oil find and oil prices. Labb, Mrs. L. D., 1/6/1891. Cleveland, Ohio. Asks for check. Lamb, H., 8/10/1889. Augusta, Georgia. Seeks loan for wholesale grocery business. Lamotte, T. A., 8/9/1893. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Skating equipment manufacturing investment. Lamprecht Brothers & Company, 1/18/1893. New York, New York. Offer securities; New Haven & West Haven Horse Railroad Company; municipal bonds; bankers. Landell, W. I., 3/24/1891. Tacoma, Washington. Home furnishings dealer investment offer. Langl, E., 3/31/1890. New York, New York. Printing company consolidation investment offer. Lanyon, J. B., 9/19/1890. Englewood, Illinois. Western mineral lands offer. H. Lapsley & Company, 1/24/1888. New York, New York. Railroad bonds; brokers. Lattenberger, C. C., 10/18/1889. Nashville, Tennessee. Nashville Pottery Company investment offer. Larremore, W., 4/11/1888. New York, New York. Attorney; regarding Dr. [Thomas?] Armitage's account. Lawrence, W. A., 1887-1891. New York, New York. Investment offers; Natural Gas Trust; broker. Lawson, L. M., 1889-1890. New York, New York. Banker; Kansas City, Missouri water works investment; Pillsbury flour mills consolidation. Lathrop, Smith & Oliphant, 1888. New York, New York. Investment offer; railroad bonds.
    - Leather Manufacturers' National Bank, 1883-1890; 56 Pages (Reel 6, Frame 0764, Box 80, Folder 597)
      New York, New York. Deposit slips; Edwin Butler letters informing John D. Rockefeller his account is overdrawn.
    - Leatherbee - Lockhart, 41 Pages (Reel 6, Frame 0820, Box 80, Folder 598)
      Leatherbee, W. A., 11/16/1891. Boston, Massachusetts. Lumber company investment in West Virginia. Le Cronier, G., 8/9-13/1890. New York, New York. Proposes purchase of Union Ferry Company of Brooklyn. Lee, M. G., 7/29/1893-8/15/1893. Terre Haute, Indiana. Oil lands in Wyoming. Leech, M. F., 7/11/1889-9/1/1889. Boulder, Colorado. Mining property in Idaho. Leonard, Georgia F., 8/21/1888. Cambridgeport, Massachusetts. Requests donation for Clinton College, Clinton, Kentucky. Leslie, D. E., 1883-1889. Cleveland, Ohio. Standard Oil Company accountant and auditor; John D. Rockefeller accounts with Standard Oil Company. Leverich, C. D., 7/1/1889. New York, New York. Offers brokerage service. Lewis, Henry, 1887-1888. New York, New York. Reports on oil market activity and oil prices. Lewis, Mrs. J. B., 5/3/1886. New York, New York. Requests interview. Leypoldt, F., 3/7/1887. Milwaukee, Wisconsin. Offers Metropolitan Iron & Land Company stock. Libbey, W., 2/16/1893. New York, New York. Requests letter of introduction for his son in Cuba. Lincoln, G. H., 1890-1893. New York, New York. Offers Standard Oil Trust stock; market conditions. Lindburgh, W., 5/5/1890. Jersey City, New Jersey. Offers investment antimony mines in Arizona. Little, S., 7/8/1889. New York, New York. Cement source investment proposal. Lockhart, C., 7/6/1885. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Coded message.
    - Logan, T. M., 1883-1888; 117 Pages (Reel 6, Frame 0861, Box 80, Folder 599)
      New York, New York. Richmond & Danville Railroad Company; Richmond & West Point Terminal Railway & Warehouse Company; John D. Rockefeller investment; negotiations over stock subscriptions; trading on inside information; earnings data; market manipulation; dissident shareholders committee.
    - Lombard - Lysle, 29 Pages (Reel 6, Frame 0978, Box 80, Folder 600)
      Lombard, W. A., 7/5/1893. New York, New York. Banker; offers stock in banks in Washington and Texas. Long, E. C., 8/29/1893. St. Paul, Minnesota. Financial assistance request; railway and building contractors. Long, J. S., 12/2/1889. Louisville, Kentucky. Long Island, New York, real estate offer. Lothridge, A. L., 12/1886-2/1889. New York, New York. Setting appointment; thanks for Standard Oil Trust stock distribution to employees. Lounsbery & Company, 1/19/1888. New York, New York. Offers stock in Utah mining companies; broker; Daly Mining Company. Benjamin E. Lower & Company, 3/24/1890. Denver, Colorado. Offers investments in real estate mortgages and mining stocks; Magnolia Gold & Silver Mining Company. Lunty, D., 4/28/1891. Cleveland, Ohio. Rental of safe deposit box; Savings & Trust Company. Lysle, R., 5/29/1889. Tiffin, Ohio. Offers real estate; board of trade secretary.
    - MacArthur - Marston, 138 Pages (Reel 7, Frame 0001, Box 80, Folder 601)